livemocha.com 2017-11-18

# Rosetta Stone Website Privacy Policy

                       Rosetta Stone Website Privacy Policy
Rosetta Stone Ltd. (“Rosetta Stone”) is the developer of the Rosetta Stone® technology-based
learning solutions. We take the privacy of our customers seriously. We are committed to
safeguarding your privacy while providing a personalized and valuable service.
Para la versión en español, haga clic aquí
Overview
This Privacy Policy statement explains the data processing practices of Rosetta Stone. If you
have any requests concerning your personal information or any questions about these practices
please contact our Privacy Officer by e-mail at privacyofficer@RosettaStone.com. We
encourage you to periodically review this statement as it may change at any time at our sole
discretion.
Our site contains links to third party sites, which are not subject to this privacy policy. Rosetta
Stone does not endorse and is not responsible for the privacy practices or content on these sites.
We recommend that you read the privacy policy of any such sites that you visit.
Information provided by you may be requested from one of our websites under the Rosetta Stone
or Rosetta World brand names, or from one of our reputable co-marketing partner sites that
represent our brands on their own websites under their company and/or brand name. In the event
that you provide us with personal information for the purposes of free registration and you later
make a purchase, whether directly from us or facilitated by one of our e-commerce partners, your
privacy rights will be protected according to our stated policies and the stated privacy policies of
these partners, which will be posted and available for your review at the time of purchase.
Information Collected
Personal information is collected by Rosetta Stone. We collect personally identifiable
information about you (your “Data”) through:
       The use of inquiry and registration forms.
       The purchase process when you buy any of our products or services
       The provision of your details to us either online or offline
The elements of your Data that we collect may include:
       Name
       Job title
       Company name
       Home, shipping and billing addresses, phone and fax number
       Mobile telephone number
       E-mail address
       IP address and browser information

       Payment details such as credit card information
       Market research data such as customer usage patterns
Use and Disclosure of Personal Information
We use your Data for purposes which may include:
       Providing our customers with a personalized service.
       Processing orders, registrations and inquiries.
       Conducting market research surveys.
       Running competitions.
       Measuring interest in and improving our website, products, and services.
       Providing you with information about products and services we offer. You may stop the
        delivery of marketing emails by following the instructions accompanying a particular
        communication or by contacting us at privacyofficer@RosettaStone.com.
       Resolving disputes, collecting fees, and troubleshooting problems.
We use the information you provide when placing an order to complete that order. We do not
share this information with outside parties except 1. To the extent necessary to complete that
order or to provide services where the outside party is acting on our behalf and has no
independent right to use the information we provide (e.g., third-party shipping, business analytics,
or customer support ), or 2. To successors in title to our business, or 3. In accordance with legal
and regulatory requirements, or 4. As necessary, in Rosetta Stone’s sole discretion, to protect the
perceived rights, safety and property of Rosetta Stone, users of our websites, and the public, or 5.
With the parent organization, affiliate or subsidiary entities of Rosetta Stone to manage and
control Data as joint users.
Other than as set out above, you will be notified when Personal Information about you will be
shared with third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to have us share such
information.
We also use information in aggregate form (so that no individual user is identified):
       To build up marketing profiles
       To aid strategic development
       To audit usage of the site
Use and Disclosure of Personal Information in Japan
In Japan, in addition to the foregoing, we may also share Data collected through digital
distribution marketplaces like the Apple App Store with Joint Providers. “Joint Providers” are
those companies which we’ve partnered with to offer, support, or manage Rosetta Stone and/or
Joint Provider Accounts, products or services, and to manage and control Data, subject to
Rosetta Stone and/or Joint Provider privacy policies.
In Japan, the Joint Provider in charge of managing jointly used Data is Sourcenext Corporation.

Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Devices
We use cookies and other tracking devices, including local shared objects written with Adobe
flash technology (flash cookies), to help personalize your use of our sites. A cookie is a small
piece of information which is sent to your computer’s hard drive by the web server so that the
website can remember who you are. This information may include information relating to your
use of our sites, information about your computer such as the computer’s IP address and browser
type, demographic data and, if you arrived at our site via a link from a third party site, the URL
of the linking page. We do not use any tracking devices to track your usage of the Internet on
other sites not operated by Rosetta Stone. If you are a registered user this may include your
name and email address for verification purposes.
We use information from cookies for purposes which may include:
       Identifying returning users and registrants
       Enabling you to move more easily around our site
       Tracking your use of our site to better develop our sites in accordance with your
        requirements
       Building up a demographic profile
       If you do not want to help us learn how to improve our site, products, offers and
        marketing strategy, you may choose to set your Web browser to not accept cookies.
        Further information on how to prevent cookies from being stored on your computer can
        be found on http://www.allaboutcookies.org under the ‘manage cookies’ section.
        Alternatively, go to the help menu within your Internet browser. Flash cookies may be
        removed using the latest versions of Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, and Microsoft
        Internet Explorer, which you may upgrade to on these browsers, or you may remove or
        block flash cookies by going to Adobe’s Website Storage Settings Panel.
From time to time we may permit third party companies to set cookies on Rosetta Stone sites for
purposes which may include market research, revenue tracking or to improve functionality of the
site.
Security Policy
Rosetta Stone has appropriate measures in place to help ensure that our users’ Data is protected
against unauthorized access or use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction and accidental
loss. Although we make reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Information from loss,
misuse, or alteration by third parties, you should be aware that there is always some risk involved
in transmitting information over the Internet. There is also some risk that thieves could find a
way to thwart our security systems.
Transfer of Data
The Internet is a global environment. Using the Internet to collect and process personal Data
necessarily involves the transmission of Data on an international basis. For individuals located
in the European Union, we participate in the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework

(the "Framework") as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection,
use and retention of personal data from the European Union and Switzerland. For more
information about our certification to the Framework, please click here:
http://www.rosettastone.com/privacy-shield, or to visit the U.S Department of Commerce site
please click here: https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome.
Access to Data and Contact Info
You may request a copy or send a correction of the personal information we hold about you by
contacting the Privacy Officer at privacyofficer@RosettaStone.com or writing to:
Privacy Officer
Rosetta Stone Ltd.
135 West Market Street
Harrisonburg VA 22801
USA
We may charge the allowable fee under applicable law for provision of this information.
Children Under 13
We do not intentionally collect any information on children under 13 years of age. We will
undertake to delete any details of such users where a parent or guardian has notified us that any
such details have been obtained.
Changes to this Policy
This policy is effective June 28, 2017. From time to time we may make changes to this privacy
policy statement to reflect any changes to our privacy practices in accordance with changes in
legislation, best practice or website enhancements. We will notify you about material changes to
this Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the email address you provided to us or by placing a
prominent notice on our website.

            Política de privacidad del sitio web de Rosetta Stone
Rosetta Stone Ltd. (“Rosetta Stone”) es el desarrollador de las soluciones de aprendizaje basadas
en tecnología Rosetta Stone®. Tomamos muy en serio la privacidad de nuestros clientes. Nos
hemos comprometido a proteger su privacidad mientras le ofrecemos un servicio valioso y
personalizado.
Descripción general
La declaración de esta Política de privacidad describe las prácticas de procesamiento de datos de
Rosetta Stone. Si desea solicitar algo en relación con su información personal o tiene alguna
pregunta sobre estas prácticas, envíe un correo electrónico a nuestro director de privacidad a
privacyofficer@RosettaStone.com. Lo invitamos a que revise con frecuencia esta declaración, ya
que podemos modificarla en cualquier momento a nuestro absoluto criterio.
Nuestro sitio contiene enlaces a sitios de terceros, que no están sujetos a esta política de
privacidad. Rosetta Stone no avala las prácticas de privacidad ni el contenido de dichos sitios, y
tampoco se responsabiliza por ellos. Le recomendamos leer la política de privacidad de los sitios
mencionados que visite.
Los sitios web de la marca Rosetta Stone o Rosetta World, o alguno de nuestros prestigiosos
socios de comercialización conjunta que representan nuestras marcas en sus sitios web bajo sus
propias marcas o compañías, pueden solicitar información suministrada por usted. En el caso de
que usted nos suministre información personal para registrarse de forma gratuita y
posteriormente haga una compra, directamente a nosotros o a través de uno de nuestros socios de
comercio electrónico, sus derechos de privacidad serán protegidos de acuerdo con nuestras
políticas y las políticas de privacidad de dichos socios, las cuales estarán publicadas y
disponibles para su lectura al momento de la compra.
Información recopilada
Rosetta Stone recopila información personal. Nosotros recopilamos información de
identificación personal sobre usted (sus “Datos”) a través de:
       El uso de formularios de registro y consultas;
       El proceso de compra cuando usted adquiere cualquiera de nuestros productos o servicios;
       El suministro de datos en línea o por otro medio por parte de usted.
Los Datos que recopilamos de usted pueden incluir lo siguiente:
       Nombre
       Cargo
       Nombre de la compañía
       Dirección particular, de envío y de facturación, número de teléfono y fax
       Número de teléfono móvil

       Dirección de correo electrónico
       Dirección IP e información del navegador
       Datos de pago como información de tarjetas de crédito
       Datos de investigación de mercado como patrones de uso de consumidores
Uso y divulgación de información personal
Nosotros usamos sus Datos para propósitos que pueden incluir lo siguiente:
       Ofrecer a los clientes un servicio personalizado.
       Procesar pedidos, registros y consultas.
       Llevar a cabo encuestas de investigación de mercado.
       Realizar concursos.
       Medir el interés y mejorar nuestro sitio web y los productos y servicios.
       Proporcionarle información sobre los productos y servicios que ofrecemos. Si desea dejar
        de recibir correos electrónicos de comercialización, siga las instrucciones de la
        comunicación        en       particular     o      comuníquese       con      nosotros      a
        privacyofficer@RosettaStone.com;
       Resolver conflictos, cobrar cargos o solucionar problemas.
La información que usted suministra al hacer un pedido, se utiliza para procesar ese pedido.
Nosotros no compartimos esa información con terceros, excepto en los siguientes casos: 1. En la
medida en que sea necesario para procesar el pedido o brindar servicios en los que un tercero
actúe en nuestro nombre y no tenga el derecho independiente a usar la información que
suministramos (p. ej., terceros que se encargan del envío, el análisis de negocios o la atención al
cliente), o 2.A sucesores legítimos de nuestra empresa, o 3. De conformidad con los requisitos
legales y regulatorios, o 4. Si es necesario, a criterio absoluto de Rosetta Stone, para proteger los
derechos percibidos, la seguridad y la propiedad de Rosetta Stone, los usuarios de nuestros sitios
web y el público en general, o 5. Con la empresa matriz o las afiliadas o subsidiarias de Rosetta
Stone para la administración y el control de los Datos como usuarios conjuntos.
Excepto en los casos mencionados, antes de compartir información personal de usted con
terceros, recibirá una notificación y tendrá la oportunidad de solicitar que no lo hagamos.
También usamos información en forma agrupada (para que no se identifique a ninguna persona
en particular):
       Para crear perfiles de comercialización
       Para contribuir al desarrollo estratégico
       Para auditar el uso del sitio
Uso y Divulgación de Información Personal en Japón
En Japón, además de lo anterior, también podemos compartir datos recopilados a través de
mercados de distribución digital como la App Store de Apple con Proveedores Conjuntos.
"Proveedores Conjuntos" son aquellas compañías con las que hemos colaborado para ofrecer,

soporte, o administrar cuentas, productos o servicios de Rosetta Stone y / o Proveedores
Conjuntos, y para administrar y controlar Data, sujeto a la privacidad de Rosetta Stone y / o
Proveedores Conjuntos Políticas.
En Japón, el Proveedor Conjunto encargado de administrar los Datos utilizados conjuntamente es
SourceNext Corporation.
Uso de cookies y otros dispositivos de seguimiento
Para personalizar el uso de nuestros sitios, usamos cookies y otros dispositivos de seguimiento
que incluyen objetos locales compartidos creados con tecnología Adobe Flash (cookies flash).
Una cookie es una pequeña cantidad de información que el servidor web envía al disco duro de
su computadora para que el sitio web pueda recordar quién es usted. Esta información puede
incluir datos relacionados con el uso que usted hace de nuestros sitios, información sobre su
computadora como la dirección IP y el tipo de navegador, datos demográficos y, si accede a
nuestro sitio a través de un enlace ubicado en un sitio de terceros, la URL de la página que
contiene dicho enlace. Los dispositivos de seguimiento no se usan para registrar el uso de
Internet en otros sitios no operados por Rosetta Stone. Si es un usuario registrado, la información
de cookies puede incluir su nombre y dirección de correo electrónico para fines de verificación.
La información de cookies se puede utilizar para los siguientes propósitos:
       Identificar a personas registradas o a usuarios que vuelven a ingresar
       Permitirle navegar con más facilidad en nuestro sitio
       Hacer un seguimiento del uso del sitio para mejorar el desarrollo de nuestros sitios de
        acuerdo con sus necesidades
       Crear un perfil demográfico
       Si no desea ayudarnos a saber cómo mejorar el sitio y nuestros productos, ofertas y
        estrategia de comercialización, puede configurar su navegador web para no aceptar
        cookies. Podrá encontrar más información sobre cómo evitar el almacenamiento de
        cookies en la computadora en http://www.allaboutcookies.org, en la sección “Manage
        cookies” (Administrar cookies). También, puede ir al menú de ayuda de su navegador de
        Internet. Las cookies flash se pueden eliminar usando las últimas versiones de Google
        Chrome, Mozilla Firefox y Microsoft Internet Explorer, que se pueden actualizar en estos
        navegadores, o también puede eliminarlas o bloquearlas desde el Panel de Configuración
        de almacenamiento de sitios web de Adobe.
Ocasionalmente, podemos permitir a compañías de terceros instalar cookies en los sitios de
Rosetta Stone para fines de investigación de mercado, seguimiento de ingresos o para mejorar la
funcionalidad del sitio.
Política de seguridad
Rosetta Stone ha implementado las medidas correspondientes para proteger los Datos de sus
usuarios contra el acceso o el uso no autorizado, la alteración, la destrucción accidental o ilícita y
la pérdida accidental. Si bien hacemos esfuerzos razonables para proteger su información

personal contra la pérdida, el uso indebido o la alteración por parte de terceros, debe saber que la
transmisión de información por Internet siempre conlleva riesgos. También existe el riesgo de
que nuestros sistemas de seguridad sean boicoteados por ladrones.
Transferencia de datos
La Internet es un entorno mundial. El uso de Internet para recopilar y procesar Datos personales
implica, necesariamente, la transmisión de Datos a nivel internacional. En lo que atañe a
personas radicadas en la Unión Europea, participamos en el Acuerdo de escudo de la privacidad
entre EE. UU. y Suiza y entre EE. UU. y la UE (“Acuerdo”), tal como lo establece el
Departamento de Comercio de EE. UU. con respecto a la recopilación, el uso y la retención de
datos personales provenientes de Suiza y la Unión Europea. Para obtener más información sobre
nuestra certificación en el Acuerdo, haga clic aquí: http://www.rosettastone.com/privacy-shield,
o visite el sitio del Departamento de Comercio de EE. UU. en:
https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome.
Acceso a datos y a información de contacto
Si desea solicitar una copia o enviar una corrección de la información personal que tenemos
sobre usted, comuníquese con el director de privacidad a privacyofficer@RosettaStone.com, o
diríjase por escrito a:
Privacy Officer
Rosetta Stone Ltd.
135 West Market Street
Harrisonburg VA 22801
USA
Por el suministro de dicha información, se podrá cobrar un cargo según lo permitan las leyes
aplicables.
Menores de 13 años
Nosotros no recopilamos de manera intencional información sobre personas menores de 13 años.
En los casos en que un padre o tutor nos notifique que se han recopilado datos de este tipo,
procederemos a eliminar tales datos.
Cambios en esta política
Esta política entra en vigencia a partir del 28 de junio de 2017. Cada cierto tiempo, podemos
hacer modificaciones en la declaración de esta política de privacidad a fin de reflejar los cambios
que hubiere en nuestras prácticas de privacidad, en consonancia con los cambios en la legislación,
las mejores prácticas o las mejoras del sitio web. Cuando haya cambios sustanciales en esta
Política de privacidad, le enviaremos una notificación a la dirección de correo electrónico que
nos suministró o publicaremos un aviso destacado en nuestro sitio web.
